theitjobboard.com 2016-11-19

# Yahoo Privacy Policy

Please read this policy to understand what information Yahoo (including Overture Services, Inc.) collects, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the use and sharing of your information when using the Yahoo Advertising Solutions (YAS) sites as a visitor. The YAS sites include sites that are branded "Yahoo Advertising Solutions" and "Yahoo Search Marketing" as well as sites on the following domains: [www.overture.com](http://www.overture.com/), [advertising.yahoo.com](http://advertising.yahoo.com/), [apt.yahoo.com](http://apt.yahoo.com/), [solutions.yahoo.com](http://solutions.yahoo.com/), and [summitseries.yahoo.com](http://summitseries.yahoo.com/). For more information on Yahoo's other privacy policies that apply to subscribers and users of other Yahoo products and services, including the Yahoo Shopping, Travel and Directory Submit programs, please read the [Yahoo Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/).

What this policy covers

This policy covers business contact information, such as name, email address, telephone number and address and other work-related information, that visitors provide to YAS online on publicly available YAS sites (where advertiser login is not required). If you are a business enrolled in advertiser programs that are subject to the Advertiser Master Services Terms and Conditions, Insertion Order(s) or other advertising or marketing agreements (collectively, "Advertising Agreement"), please refer to your Advertising Agreement to learn more about how Yahoo may use information about your business. The terms of such business agreements supersede the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

Types of information we collect and how we use it

The following describes what information Yahoo Advertising Solutions collects from visitors to the YAS sites as well as outside the Yahoo network of web sites, and how we may use it:

  1. Email addresses and related information  
There may be opportunities for visitors to the site to sign-up to receive email communications. Visitors may subscribe by providing an email address and other requested information. Recipients of email marketing messages will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from future messages via the link(s) provided within the message.
  2. Search  
The Overture.com site offers web search functionality to visitors. Anonymous cookies are used on the site in connection with the search functionality.
  3. Cookies and web beacons on YAS web sites  
Yahoo accesses [Yahoo cookies](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/cookies/details.html) and may use [Yahoo web beacons](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/beacons/details.html) when you visit the YAS sites or other sites on the Yahoo domain. Yahoo and certain partners working on behalf of Yahoo, also use web beacons on the YAS sites. Yahoo may share site usage information about visitors to the YAS sites with third-party advertising companies for the purpose of targeting and measuring the effectiveness of our Internet advertisements on this site and other sites. For this purpose, Yahoo and these third-party advertising companies note some of the pages you visit on our sites through the use of web beacons.

The information collected by these third-party advertising companies through the use of these web beacons is not personally identifiable. For more information about our third-party advertisers, including how to opt out of their targeting programs, please visit their sites: [Omniture (207.net)](http://www.omniture.com/), [Commission Junction](http://www.cj.com/) and [SearchRev](http://www.searchrev.com/).

In addition to the above, Yahoo's email delivery vendor may employ web beacons and cookies within HTML email messages sent on our behalf and on the YAS sites. The use of cookies and web beacons described above help Yahoo to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use the YAS sites. 

  4. YAS cookies and web beacons outside the Yahoo network of web sites  
Yahoo Search Marketing offers advertisers tools that allow them to better understand the performance of their online marketing campaigns. For more information about these tools and the web beacons and cookies used, please read the [Yahoo Search Marketing Tools Privacy Statement](http://docs.yahoo.com/info/privacy/us/ysmt.html). 
  5. Promotions and sweepstakes  
From time to time, Yahoo may sponsor or host promotions and sweepstakes where we collect information. Use and sharing of this information will be disclosed in promotion and sweepstakes rules or on the page where you sign-up. 
  6. IP addresses and information specific to your computer  
Yahoo logs [IP](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/ip/details.html) information when you visit our sites, including the YAS sites. In addition to this information, Yahoo collects information that your computer's browser automatically reports to us such as information about your operating system and browser version. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Yahoo does not rent, sell or share personally identifiable information about visitors to the YAS sites. However, Yahoo may share this information with selected partners, vendors, agents or others who work on our behalf, in order to provide products or services you've requested, or when we have your permission. In addition, Yahoo may share information about you if Yahoo is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Yahoo will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Please note that we may also share information in the event that we are asked to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or as otherwise permitted by law. 

Other

Yahoo may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on this site. 

The YAS sites are not targeted at children and are not intended for use by children under the age of 13.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the following:

Yahoo! Inc.  
Yahoo Advertising Solutions - Privacy Policy Issues  
701 First Avenue  
Sunnyvale, CA 94089

Effective Date: July 13, 2005
